BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.1272: Champion Papers, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 507, 1966- 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code no.1273: St. Joe Paper Company, Inland Container Corporation, Mead Containers, Owens-Illinois, Inc., West Virginia Pulp and Paper and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 300, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Code no.1276: S.D. Warren Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1069, 1968- 1969 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Code no.1281: Union Camp Corporation and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 505, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 488, International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 176, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Code no.1284: Scott Paper Company and The Association of Western Pulp Workers, Locals 183, 644, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Code no.1285: Scott Paper Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 488, 1969- 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Code no.1287: Winona Paper Box, Inc., American Paper Box Company, O.E. Clark Paper Box Company, J.V. Sparks, Inc., Papercraft Boxes, Inc., Specialty Paper Box Company and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 2, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Code no.1293: Riegel Paper Corporation and International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, AFL-CIO, Locals 738, 797, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Code no.1296: Owens-Illinois, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 453, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Code no.1301: Weyerhauser Company and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, Locals 580, 633, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Code no.1400: Chicago Newspaper Publishers' Association and Chicago Typographical Union, Local 16, 1960-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Code no.1401: Chicago Newspaper Publishers' Association and Chicago Web Printing Pressmen's Union, 1960-1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Code no.1402: Boston Daily Newspapers and Boston Typographical Union, 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Code no.1403: News Syndicate Co., Inc. and Newspaper Guild of New York, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Code no.1404: The New York Times Company and Newspaper Guild of New York, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Code no.1405: The Publishers' Association of New York City and New York Typographical Union, Local 6, 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Code no.1406: The Publishers' Association of New York City and New York Newspaper Printing and Pressmen's Union, Local 2, 1958- 1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Code no.1407: The Publishers' Association of New York City and Newspaper and Mail Deliverer's Union of New York and Vicinity, 1960- 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Code no.1409: McCall Corporation and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1959-1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Code no.1410: McCall Corporation and The Dayton Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union, Local 54, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Code no.1411: Chicago Lithographers Association and Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 4, 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Code no.1412: Franklin Association of Chicago and Bookbinders' and Papercutters' Union of Chicago, Local 8, 1960-1972 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Code no.1414: Franklin Association of Chicago and Chicago Typographical Union, Local 16, 1960-1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Code no.1415: Graphic Arts Employers' Association of San Francisco and Bookbinders' and Bindery Women's Union, 1958-1970 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Code no.1416: Graphic Arts Employers' Association of San Francisco and Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 17, 1959-1967 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Code no.1418: The Lithographers' Association of Philadelphia and Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union, Local 14, 1959- 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Code no.1419: The Metropolitan Lithographers' Association and Amalgamated Lithographers of America, Local 1, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Code no.1420: Printers' League (Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc.) and New York Typographical Union, Local 6, 1959- 1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Code no.1421: Printers' League (Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc.) and New York Press Assistants' and Offset Workers' Union, Local 23, 1960-1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Code no.1423: Printers' League (Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc.) and New York Paper Cutters' and Bookbinders' Union, Local 119, 1960-1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Code no.1424: Trade Bindery, Lithographer and Printing Employers and Los Angeles Bookbinders and Binderywomens' Union, Local 63, 1959- 1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Code no.1425: Allied Printing Employers' Association and Philadelphia Printing Pressmen's Union, Local 4, Philadelphia Press Assistant's Union, Local 11, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Code no.1426: Western Printing and Lithographic Company and International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, Local 13, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Code no.1428: The Edition Bookbinders of New York, Inc. and Bookbinders and Machine Operators Union, Local 25 (International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, AFL-CIO), 1958-1971 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Code no.1429: Bindery Union, Graphic Arts Association of Michigan and Detroit Bindery Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 20, 1961- 1972 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Code no.1431: Allied Printing Employers' Association and Bookbinders' and Bindery Women's Union, Local 2, 1960-1968 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Code no.1432: Wilson Jones Company and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Locals 148, 148e, 1960-1965 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Code no.1433: Photo-Engravers Board of Trade of New York, Inc. and New York Lithographers and Photo-Engravers Union, Local 1, 1961- 1970 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- CARDS (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code no.1435: Printing Industry of the Twin Cities and Lithographers and Photo-Engravers International Union, Local 229, 1966- 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code no.1437: Commercial Printing Employers of Los Angeles and Los Angeles Typographical Union, Local 174, 1963-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code no.1438: Time, Inc. and Newspaper Guild of New York, 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code no.1440: Brown and Bigelow and Bookbinders Specialty Workers and Miscellaneous Helpers Union, Local 14, 1965-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Code no.20: The Dow Chemical Company and International Union of District 50 Allied and Technical Workers, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Code no.243: Pet, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 22, 23, 61, 71, 332, 509, 592, 882, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Code no.293: The Amalgamated Sugar Company and The American Federation of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Code no.612: Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Code no.889: Smith Brothers Manufacturing Company and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Code no.1258: Inland Container Corporation and United Papermakers and Paperworkers, AFL-CIO, Locals 31,114,1046, 993, 4658, 783, 737, 954, 828, 1961-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Code no.1422: Printers' League (Printing Industries of Metropolitan New York, Inc.) and New York Printing Pressmens' Union, Local 51, 1962- 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Code no.1633: E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company and Seaford Nylon Employees' Council, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Code no.1644: Merck and Co., Inc. and Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers' International Union, Local 8-575, 1964-1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Code no.1822: Phillips Petroleum Company and International Union of Operating Engineers, AFL-CIO, Local 351, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Code no.2572: The Symington Wayne (Symington Gould) Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1956-1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Code no.2973: Norris Industries and (The International Union of) United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 509, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Code no.3724: The Leviton Manufacturing Co., Inc. and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Code no.4050: Bell Aerospace Corporation and (The International Union of) United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 218, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Code no.4067: McDonnell Douglas Corporation and Southern California Professional Engineering Association, 1965-1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Code no.4147: Bell Aerospace Corporation and (The International Union of) United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America AND United Office Workers, UAW, Local 317, 1966-1972 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Code no.5789: New York Local Television Broadcasting and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1963-1972 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Code no.6003: Atlantic City Electric Company and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 210, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Code no.6013: Florida Power Corporation and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Locals 433, 626, 1412, 1491, 1967- 1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Code no.316: National Distillers Products Company and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 5, 11, 20, 24, 32, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Code no.318: Northwest Brewers Association and (Brewery Workers) Joint Council of Teamsters, Locals 28, 37, 1960-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Code no.319: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, AFL-CIO, Local 28, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Code no.320: Schenley Distillers, Inc. and Distillery Workers, Local 266, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Code no.321: Seagram Distillers Company and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 7, 10, 13, 16, 34, 52, 109, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Code no.323: Winery Employers Association and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, Locals 45, 186, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Code no.325: N/A and Beef Boners and Sausage Makers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 100, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Code no.327: The Colorado Milling and Elevator Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, AFL-CIO, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Code no.328: The Great Western Sugar Company and Teamsters, Warehousemen and Sugar Workers, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Code no.330: The Carnation Company and Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Locals 783, 823, 327, 455, 579, 695, 745, 984, 619, 650, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Code no.329: Chicago Bakery Employers' Labor Council and Bakery, Cracker, Pie and Yeast Wagon Drivers Union (Teamsters), Local 734, 1961- 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Code no.331: Ice Cream Manufacturers and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Union, Local 471, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Code no.333: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and General Warehousemen's Union (Teamsters), Local 852, 1962- 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Code no.335: Food Employers Council of Los Angeles and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 848, 166, 186, 572, 952, 982, 1962- 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Code no.336: Country Milk Plant Labor Committee and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1959-1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Code no.338: California Packing Corporation and International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 11, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Code no.339: Seattle Bakers Bureau, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America, Local 9, 1962- 1964 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Code no.340: Packing House Agreement of Chicago and Vicinity and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 710, 1961- 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Code no.341: Milk Dealers of Philadelphia and Vicinity and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 463, 676, 331 AND International Brotherhood of Firemen, Oilers, Powerhouse Operators and Maintenance Men, Local 473, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Code no.342: N/A and Ice Cream Drivers and Ice Cream Industry Employees Union (Teamsters), Local 17, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Code no.344: Frozen Food Employers Association and California State Council of Freezer Unions (Teamsters), 1961-1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Code no.345: Chock Full O' Nuts Corporation and International Union of District 50 (United Mine Workers of America), Local 15500, 1966- 1969 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Code no.347: Loft Candy Corporation, Far Eastern Manufacturing Company and Candy and Confectionary Union, AFL-CIO, Local 50, 1958- 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Code no.348: California Bakery Employers Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Code no.349: Dairy Employers' Labor Council and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 38, 66, 148, 252, 378, 411, 672, 699, 951, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Code no.350: The Nestle Company and P.C.K. Employees Union, 1966-1972 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Code no.351: Philadelphia Lager Beer Brewers' Association and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft-Drink and Distillery Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Locals 5, 183, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Code no.352: Brood Products Company and Cannery, Citrus Workers, Drivers, Warehousemen and Allied Employees, Local 60, 1965- 1971 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Code no.353: N/A and Milk, Ice Cream Drivers and Dairy Employees' Union, Local 39, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Code no.354: The Smithfield Packing Company and Employees Beneficial Association, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Code no.355: Metropolitan Milk Industry and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 388, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Code no.357: California Packing Corporation and Fruit and Vegetable Packers and Warehousemen Union, Local 760, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Code no.359: The Coca-Cola Bottling Company of New York, Inc. and Brewery Soft Drink Workers and Drivers, Local 134, 1963-1966 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Code no.364: Morton Frozen Foods and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 29, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Code no.365: N/A and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 93, 166, 186, 572, 683, 871, 898, 952, 982, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Code no.366: Brown-Fordman Distillers Corporation and Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America, AFL-CIO, Local 39, 1968-1972 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Code no.368: Kuner-Empson Company and Warehouse and Distribution Employees Union, Local 452, 1967-1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Code no.369: Campbell Soup Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local P-1229, 1966-1973 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Code no.371: N/A and Soft Drink Drivers and Helpers, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 744, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Code no.372: Campbell Soup Company and Food Handlers Union, Local 425, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1967-1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Code no.373: General Foods Corporation and Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 56, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Code no.374: Ralston Purina Company and United Cannery and Industrial Workers of the Pacific, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Code no.375: American Home Foods, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 38, 1969- 1971 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Code no.377: Oscar Mayer and Co., Inc. and Beef Boners and Sausage Makers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 100 AND Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Code no.379: California Bakery Employers Association and Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America, Local 24, 1970- 1972 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Code no.380: Seabrook Farms Co., Inc. and Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 56, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Code no.382: Stokley-Van Camp, Inc. and The International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 487, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Code no.390: Milk Dealers of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Food Driver-Salesmen, Dairy and Ice Cream Workers Union (Teamsters), Locals 463, 331 AND Truck Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 676, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Code no.391: Rockingham Poultry Marketing Cooperative, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Allied Workers of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 593, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Code no.397: Ore-Ida Foods, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 218, 1966- 1971 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Code no.403: Memphis Bakery Employers' Association and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 149, 1966- 1969 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Code no.500: The American Tobacco Company and Tobacco Workers' International Union, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Code no.501: The American Tobacco Company and Tobacco Workers' International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 182, 183, 192, 1962- 1967 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Code no.828: National Skirt and Sportswear Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Skirt and Sportswear Workers' Union, Local 23, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Code no.829: National Women's' Neckwear and Scarf Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Ladies' Neckwear Workers' Union of Greater New York, Local 142, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Code no.830: Needle Trades Employers Association and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 178, 361, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Code no.831: New England Sportswear Manufacturers' Association and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Cloak, Skirt, and Dressmakers' Union, Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73, 80, 1958-1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Code no.832: New Jersey Apparel Contractors Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Local 220, 1961- 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Code no.833: Philadelphia Apparel Producers Association and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Philadelphia Dress Joint Board, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Code no.834: The Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Code no.835: United Better Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Code no.836: Popular Price Dress Contractors Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Code no.837: Allied Underwear Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Code no.838: Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Corset and Brassiere Workers of New York, Local 32 AND Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, 1953-1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Code no.839: The Lingerie Manufacturers Association of New York, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62 AND Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Code no.840: Maidenform, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Code no.841: Maidenform, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Code no.843: Undergarment Accessories Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Undergarment and Negligee Workers' Union, Local 62, 1960-1963 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Code no.844: Eastern Women's Headwear Association, Inc. AND American Millinery Manufacturers Association, Inc. and United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union AND Joint board of Millinery Workers Unions, Locals 2, 24, 42, 57, 90, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Code no.846: The John B. Stetson Company and United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers International Union AND Joint board of Millinery Workers Unions, Local 60, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Code no.848: Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc. and Children's Dress, House Dress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, Local 91 AND Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Code no.847: Children's Dress, Cotton Dress and Sportswear Contractors Association, Inc. and Children's Dress, House Dress and Bathrobe Makers' Union, Local 91 AND Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters Union, Local 10, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Code no.849: Industrial Association of Juvenile Apparel Manufacturers, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1961- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Code no.850: Infant and Juvenile Manufacturers' Association and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Local 169, 1965- 1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Code no.851: Infants and Children's Novelties Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 105, 10, 1956- 1964 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Code no.852: Infants and Children's Novelties Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 105, 10, 1956- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Code no.853: Associated Fur Manufacturers, Inc. and Furriers Joint Council of New York (United Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1961-1969 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Code no.854: Belt Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Belt Makers' Union, Local 40, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Code no.855: Shirt, Robe and Leisurewear Apparel Association of America, Inc. and Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1958-1969 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Code no.857: Plastic Soft Materials Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Rubberized Novelty and Plastic Fabric Workers' Union, Local 98, 1960-1972 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Code no.858: Slate Belt Apparel Contractors Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1960-1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Code no.859: Women's Apparel and Shoulder Pad Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, Local 142, 1959- 1961 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Code no.860: Pleaters, Stitchers and Embroiderers Association, Inc. and (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) Bonnaz, Embroiderers, Tucking, Pleating and Allied Crafts Union, Local 66, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Code no.862: New England Apparel Manufacturers' Association, Inc. and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 178, 361, 324, 232, 1961-1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Code no.863: Hickok Manufacturing Company, Inc. and Rochester Independent Union, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Code no.864: I.B. Kleinert Rubber Company and American Federation of Rubber Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 20499, 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Code no.868: N/A and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 101, 213, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Code no.869: H.W. Gossard Company and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Locals 286, 392, 547, 572, 1963-1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Code no.870: Alabama Textile Products Corporation AND The Andala Company and Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1965- 1967 (Box 10, Folder 36)